question_data = [
    {"question": "A slug's blood is green.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The loudest animal is the African Elephant.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Approximately one quarter of human bones are in the feet.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "The total surface area of a human lungs is the size of a football pitch.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In West Virginia, USA, if you accidentally hit an animal with your car, "
             "you are free to take it home to eat.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "In London, UK, if you happen to die in the House of Parliament, you are entitled "
             "to a state funeral.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "It is illegal to pee in the Ocean in Portugal.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "You can lead a cow down stairs but not up stairs.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "Google was originally called 'Backrub'.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "Buzz Aldrin's mother's maiden name was 'Moon'.", "correct_answer": "True"},
    {"question": "No piece of square dry paper can be folded in half more than 7 times.", "correct_answer": "False"},
    {"question": "A few ounces of chocolate can to kill a small dog.", "correct_answer": "True"}
]

data_trivia = [{"type": "boolean",
         "difficulty": "easy",
         "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
         "question": "Salt is 100% composed of Sodium.",
         "correct_answer": "False",
        "incorrect_answers": ["True"]
         },
        {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
           "question": "Not including false teeth; A human has two sets of teeth in their lifetime.",
           "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
          {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
           "question": "Igneous rocks are formed by excessive heat and pressure.",
           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
          {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
           "question": "An average human can go two weeks without water.",
           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
          {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
           "question": "An exothermic reaction is a chemical reaction that releases energy by radiating electricity.",
           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
          {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
           "question": "Celiac Disease is a disease that effects the heart, causing those effected to be unable to eat meat.",
           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
          {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
           "question": "Water always boils at 100&deg;C, 212&deg;F, 373.15K, no matter where you are.",
           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
          {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
           "question": "Psychology is the science of behavior and mind.",
           "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
          {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
           "question": "An Astronomical Unit is the distance between Earth and the Moon.",
           "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
          {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Science &amp; Nature",
           "question": "An atom contains a nucleus.", "correct_answer": "True",
           "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
